ANDREA MOLNÁR

UX/UI Designer

+39 339 591 6612

hey.andrea.molnar@gmail.com

andi-sketches.github.io/portfolio

Milan, Italy



I am a UX/UI designer in the making, with plenty of curiosity to learn more about the art of creating intuitive and beautiful designs. I also like to try my hand at coding up the results! See my portfolio on the above link. After completing my Bachelor's degree and 2 years of working in Product Marketing in Berlin, I decided to move to sunny Italy to enrol in the MSc program for Human-Computer Interaction at the University of Trento. As I'm finishing degree now, I'm open for internship opportunities.

EDUCATION

Human-Computer Interaction, MSc

University of Trento (Trento, Italy) | 2017 - 2019

Winner of Winter School "Education as a Common Good" for project "Once upon a time..." educational card game. Current GPA: 30/30.

Selected classes:

- Social cognition and interaction design
- Affective computing
- Prototyping interactive systems

Media Management, BA

Macromedia University (Berlin, Germany) | 2012 - 2015

Thesis topic: "Gamification and Crowdsourcing in E-Learning: A Duolingo case study".

Final GPA: 28/30

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Product Marketing Manager

Babbel (Berlin, Germany) | 2016 - 2017

Founded in 2007, Babbel has developed the world's first language learning app. A leader in the digital language learning industry, it has over 1 million active subscribers. Key responsibilities included:

- Driving the research and development of new product features in collaboration with the User Research and Product Design, as well as coordinating their roll-out strategy;
- Assessment and analysis of the business potential of innovation opportunities based on market conditions, the competitive landscape and customer needs.

Product Management Trainee

Crobo (Berlin, Germany) | 2015 - 2016

Crobo is a full-service digital marketing agency, with a primary focus on mobile and online games. Key responsibilities included:

- Aid in designing features for crobo's in-house affiliate platform;
- Communication between the product team and the users of the platform (announcement of updates, processing feature requests and feedback etc.).

SKILLS

UX & UI Design Process

Competitor analysis

User interview & analysis

Surveys

User research

Persona & user journey creation

Wireframing & IA

Prototyping

Usability testing

Agile development

Tools & Code

Sketch

Figma

InVision

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

LANGUAGES

English (Fluent)

Italian (Fluent)

German (Fluent)

Hungarian (Native)

Japanese (Intermediate)

INTERESTS

Photography

Literature & Theater

Hiking

